menatplay.com 2019-11-23

# PRIVACY POLICY - Pg.

_Last revised on April 15, 2019_

We understand the privacy of Menatplay Members is very important. During the navigation of the website and the registration process, Members may provide personally identifiable information about themselves, therefore we have developed this policy to protect Member privacy while they enjoy Menatplay.

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for menatplay.com and vod.menatplay.com and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site. It applies solely to information collected by these websites.

Company's Site contains sexually explicit material and is not intended to be viewed by anyone under the age of 18 or who has not reached the age of majority in their community. Membership and access to the Site are expressly and strictly limited to adults at least 18 years of age who have reached the age of majority in their community.

We collect several types of information from and about you, including:  
\- Your email address, password and any general payment information you submit during registration. We treat this information as "Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII".  
\- Non-personally identifiable information, such information about your computer system or device, your preferences, your online activity, and your location information ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information" a "Non-PII"). Non-PII, by itself, does not identify you, but it can be combined with other information in a way that allows you to be identified. If this happens, we will treat the combined information as PII.  
\- We use Google Analytics to collect web data that helps us analyze our web traffic and the Elevated X content-management framework.

We may collect information from or about you in the following ways:

We collect information provided by you when you (1) create your public profile; (2) communicate with us or request information about or from us by e-mail or with our Client Relations team; (3) participate in our online forums or post content on this Website ("User Contributions"), (4) fill out forms or fields on this Website; (5) sign-up for any of our newsletters, materials or our services on this Website or other sites; or (6) participate in our online surveys or questionnaires.

AUTOMATIC INFORMATION COLLECTION  
We also use automatic data collection technologies to collect and store certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns when you interact with this Website through your computer or mobile device. In addition, we may allow third-party ad networks to use automatic data collection technologies to collect similar information about you for the purposes of providing interest-based ads.

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contacts from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We use personal information to provide Members contractual access to Menatplay, to process Member authorized payments, communicate receipts, troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, enforce any agreements or policies, and to facilitate viewing of Menatplay. We may use the information collected to improve marketing, analyze site usage, improve content offerings, customize site layout and provide information about Menatplay to its Users. 

We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email:  
\- See what data we have about you if any;  
\- Change/correct any data we have about you;  
\- Have us delete any data we have about you;  
\- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, we take reasonable precautions to protect your information both online and offline. We do not store credit card information. That data is exclusively held at 

or 

, depending on which option you chose during registration.

We may disclose personal information collected if required by law, court order or other governmental authority or when We believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of Menatplay or Us.

In the event of a change of ownership (merger, acquisition or sale of assets), We reserve the right to transfer all User information collected in connection with Menatplay to such separate entity.

Members residing in the European Union may exercise their right to be forgotten in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Members must contact Client Relations providing all details necessary to identify the Member and sufficient details regarding the membership(s) they wish to be deleted. We shall comply with this request in less than thirty (30) days where the request does not prove impossible or involve disproportionate effort for Us to comply. In accordance with this same regulation, Members residing in the European Union also have the right to obtain a copy of their personal information by contacting Client Relations. Such information will be provided to the Member in digital format within less than thirty (30) days where the request does not prove impossible or involve disproportionate effort for Us to comply. Members residing in the European Union have the right to complain to the supervisory authority in their country.

YOUR RIGHTS  
Members have the right to stop receiving promotional emails from Us and may exercise this right at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email or by contacting Client Relations. Users may NOT opt out of receiving emails regarding account details such as responses to questions or membership purchase receipts. Users must directly contact Our partners or third parties from which they receive other communication for questions or to unsubscribe. 

Users have the right to withdraw their consent to processing the personal information necessary to provide access to MENATPLAY (such as debiting their payment method, streaming or downloading video and images, interacting with the website as a member). Users must contact Client Relations to withdraw this consent. Please note this will remove all access to Menatplay.

Users have the right to change their payment method where applicable (for example if their credit card expired or they wish to change the credit card associated with their Membership).

Users who wish to make a change other personal information (rectification) must create a new membership. Such Users are solely responsible to cancel the initial membership they wanted to rectify when creating a new membership.

COOKIES  
A cookie is a small file placed on your computer to help us provide you with a good online experience. It's how we distinguish you from other people that visit menatplay.com. Pretty much every site nowadays uses them for such basic necessities as "user sessions" (i.e. knowing and remembering if you are logged in or not).

We use standard 'session identification' cookies created by our content management system. These cookies are used to distinguish you from other users.

Menatplay uses Google Analytics to measure and analyze what people do on our site. This is the gold standard of online analytics tools and we use it to look at things like which pages are most popular (and which ones aren't), which browsers people use, how they arrive at our site, etc. - all of which allows us to keep improving the site and your experience.

These are all standard uses of cookies and we do not record any more information than needed or do anything out of the norm. 

Members are not obligated to accept cookies and browsers can be modified to refuse cookies. Users may also delete cookies. If all cookies are refused, many websites may not function properly, including Ours. It is possible to modify browser settings to only accept cookies with consent before each cookie is placed on the computer or device used. This provides more control over what is placed on the computer or device, however, it may slow down the web experience.

If you wish to restrict, block or delete cookies, you can do this through your web browser. Instructions for how to manage cookies for all versions of all of the major web browsers: Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, Opera, etc. can be found online with a standard search. Please remember disabling or refusing cookies may lead to many services on Menatplay being unavailable.

SECURITY  
We take reasonable precautions against external threats to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about Members, and to protect against the loss, misuse and alterations of information under Our control. Our third party payment processors provide Members with a secure web page through which billing information is submitted when purchasing a membership. All personally identifiable information held by Us is stored in a secure location (behind a firewall with limited administrative access).

Member login information must be protected by the Member. We advise all Members NOT to share username or password details with anyone. It is the Member’s responsibility to keep password information confidential. A Member's account may be deactivated for abuse if We assess a Member’s login details have been used by someone other than the registered Member to Menatplay.

UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. 

For further information, please read our 

.

Feel free to contact us at support@menatplay.com.
